rivalry.gg 2019-03-20

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This privacy policy explains what personal information Rivalry Limited (“Rivalry” or “we”) will collect from you and how we will use that personal information. We are committed to being transparent with you regarding our use of your personal information and we encourage you to contact us at privacy@rivalry.com if you have any questions.

By continuing to use the website [www.rivalry.com](https://www.rivalry.com/) (the “ **Website** ”), you consent to us obtaining and using your personal information. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, you should not continue to use the Website. You have the right to cease using the Website at any time, but as explained in paragraph 4 below, in such circumstances we may still be legally required to retain some of your personal information.

We are registered with the Isle of Man Information Commissioner under registration number N003904.

### Contents of This Privacy Notice

  1. Who controls your personal data?
  2. What personal data will we obtain from you, and how and when will we request it?
  3. Why do we obtain your personal data?
  4. Who will we share your personal data with?
  5. How do we ensure the security of your personal data?
  6. IP Addresses, Cookies and Links to Third Party Websites
  7. Access To, and Amending, Your Personal Data
  8. Closure of Your Account
  9. Amendments to This Policy
  10. Comments and Questions

### 1\. Who controls your data?

Rivalry Limited is the “data controller” as defined in the Data Protection Act 2002. This means that Rivalry will obtain and process your personal data.

### 2\. What personal data will we obtain from you, and how and when will we obtain it?

When you register for an account on the Website, **** we will ask you to you provide us with the following information:

  * Your full name;
  * Your date of birth;
  * Your gender;
  * Your address, postcode and country of residence; and
  * Your contact details (email address and telephone number).

In order to ensure that you can access all of the benefits of having an account on the Website, we may collect and process the following additional personal data about you:

  * The currency in which you hold your account currency, encrypted password, payment details, bank account details and Card details;
  * An internationally recognized photo ID (passport, driving licence), a utility bill, proof of identity, residence and/or age, and/or a bank or credit card statement relating to your payment details that are registered with us;
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
  * Information that you submit in response to a survey(s) or poll;
  * Details of transactions you carry out through the Website and your account number with us;
  * Details of your visits to the Website including, but not limited to Bets and transaction records, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access; and
  * When you make a withdrawal from your Account, we may require the following from you to effect the withdrawal and may carry out a security check:

(1) A photocopy of both sides of your Card clearly showing your signature;

(2) A photocopy of your passport or driving licence; and 

(3) A copy of your Card statement header showing your billing address; 

We reserve the right to conduct credit checks with third party credit and financial institutions in order to confirm any information that you have provided to us or to determine your ability to use the Website.

### 3\. Why do we obtain your personal information?

3.1 We will obtain and process your personal data in order to:

3.1.1 Review and determine your eligibility to use the Website or open an account with us;

3.1.2 Open, operate and manage your account;

3.1.3 Confirm the details that you have provided to us in relation to your account;

3.1.4 Perform our legal obligations to you as a user of the Website, including our obligation to provide the services on the Website;

3.1.5 Enable us to carry out statistical and other analysis;

3.1.6 Verify your age, the accuracy of your information or the processing of bets or transactions;

3.1.7 Disclose such information to third parties (including financial institutions, software providers, identity verification, age verification and credit reporting agencies) in connection with the processing of bets or transactions (please note that we will keep record of the search and the third party may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes);

3.1.8 Verify your eligibility to win or place a bet on the Website;

3.1.9 Verify the payment details that you provide to us, including the registered address of your debit or credit card(s);

3.1.10 Contact you using your contact details to tell you about changes to the Website or Services, technical or security issues, updates and changes to this Policy or our Terms;

3.1.11 Comply with our regulatory and legal obligations, including our ‘know your customer’ (KYC) and due diligence requirements;

3.1.12 Provide customer support services;

3.1.13 Ensure that content from the Website and the Services are presented in an effective manner for you and for your computer;

3.1.14 Provide you with information regarding promotional offers and our products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;

3.1.15 Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service or Website, when you choose to do so; or,

3.1.16 Reporting of crime or suspected crime, including money laundering or fraud.

3.2 We may need to request further information from you if you wish to make any withdrawals from your account, and you agree that we may contact you (using the contact details that you have provided to us) for this purpose.

3.3 If you do not wish us to process your personal data in the methods referred to in any of clauses 3.1.5; 3.1.10; 3.1.14 or 3.1.15, please do not click on the ‘opt-in’ box on the Website in relation to these purposes.

### 4\. What will we do with your personal data?

4.1 We will not disclose any personal information that you provide to us to third parties unless: (i) we have your consent; (ii) it is required or permitted by law, (iii) your agreement with us permits such disclosure; or (iv) it is in our legitimate interests to do so. This is explained more fully in clause 4.2 below.

4.2 In accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Business with you, you understand and agree that we may disclose your personal information for the following purposes to the following third parties:

4.2.1 Third party affiliates who direct users to the Website for the purposes of confirming commission or other related purposes; and

4.2.2 Other third parties for the purposes of verifying information that you provide to us (e.g. provision of information to banks for verifying credit card payments).

4.2.3 To any member of our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries;

4.2.4 To any prospective seller or buyer of any business or assets related to the Website or all or part of our business in respect of the sale or insolvency and the ultimate seller or buyer;

4.2.5 To a third party if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data with them in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, reputation, security or safety of Rivalry Limited, our Website, our customers or others; this includes (but is not limited to) exchanging information with or providing information to third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction;

4.2.6 To any operator, payment processor, verification service provider, marketing partners who provide services to us in relation to the Website or our services, including any person specifically named in our Terms of Business or in other agreements that form part of our agreement with you;

4.2.7 To any law enforcement or revenue authorities (when requested by them to do so) and only to the extent necessary to adequately deal with the requests made;

4.2.8 To your bank or card scheme operator in order to verify the Card information or bank information that you provide to us and/or to recover payments made to you in error, in accordance with our Terms of Business;

4.2.9 To any payment collection agency that we may decide to use in order to recover monies you owe to us;

4.2.10 To any Independent Betting Adjudication Service for the purposes of investigating a query made under our Terms of Business; and/or

4.2.11 To our licensor, the Isle of Man Gambling Supervision Commission (which requires unrestricted access to all player details and records in order to regulate the online gambling industry and to ensure that it is conducted honestly and fairly and remains free from criminal influence) or any other licensing or regulatory authority which we may deal with in relation to the Website.

4.2.12 To _our payment service provider MoneyMatrix Limited, Level 3A, St Julians Business Centre, Triq Elija Zammit, St Julians STJ3155, Malta (hereinafter “MoneyMatrix”)who is required by law to report any activity that raises suspicion of money laundering, funding of terrorism, or any other illegal activity. To enable MoneyMatrix to fulfil these obligations, we transmit the following data to MoneyMatrix: transaction data and KYC documents, your name and address. MoneyMatrix will only process the personal data for the above-mentioned purpose and in accordance with all applicable data protection laws._

4.3 We may also use your email address or your postal address to send you updates or news regarding the Website or the services we provide, but you can choose to stop receiving emails or post of this nature at any time by accessing your account details on the ‘Account Details’ section of the Website.

4.4 We do not sell or trade any of your personal information to third parties.

 _What happens if you agree to receive promotions from third parties?_

4.5 If you have told us (either when you registered for an account or at any later time) that you are happy to receive information or promotions from selected third parties about goods and services which may be of interest to you, you consent to us sending your information to those third parties so that they may provide you with such offers or information. You may opt out of receiving such offers or you may change your preferences at any time by accessing your account details on the Website;

 _Marketing and advertising companies:_

4.6 Except in accordance with clause 4.3 above, we will not disclose your personal information to advertising or marketing companies, but we may provide them with anonymized information about Website users. For example, we may inform them that a certain number of people of a given age have struck a bet on a particular event on the Website on any given day, or we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit the Website.

 _Transferring your personal data to other countries:_

4.7 In order to provide our services and/or operate the Website effectively, we may need to transfer data, including personal information, to other companies outside the Isle of Man or outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

4.8 If we determine that it is necessary to transfer personal data in accordance with clause 4.7, we will only make such a transfer if we are satisfied that the recipient companies offer an adequate level of protection for personal data.

4.9 You agree that we may transfer personal information we hold about you to any country (including countries outside the European Economic Area) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. How do we ensure the security of your personal data?

5.1 We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

5.2 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

5.3 We have no obligation to monitor or moderate any user’s activity or use of the Website, however we retain the right at all times to monitor, retain and disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or regulatory authority request, to ensure that the services are properly used, that our Terms of Business are being complied with or to investigate a suspected breach of our Terms of Business.

5.4 We understand that your online security is important to you and we want you to be fully satisfied that your personal details are secure before you commence activities with us.

5.5 Although we cannot completely guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website, we will do our best to protect your personal data. You must understand, however, that while we will take the steps set out in paragraph 5.4, any transmission of data by you over the internet is carried out at entirely your own risk. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorised manner.

### 6\. IP Addresses, Cookies, Links to Third-Party Websites and Call Recording

6.1 The Website may from time to time contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates as well as third party websites to which we have no affiliation. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

6.2 We may collect information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system, browser type and other individually identifiable data, for system administration, statistical and fraud prevention purposes. Such information may be used to uniquely identify users to prevent fraudulent activity and perform identity verification.

6.3 We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer hard drive. On revisiting the Website, our computer server will recognize the cookie, giving us information about your last visit. They help us to improve the Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us:

6.3.1 To estimate our user size and usage pattern;

6.3.2 To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize the Website according to your individual interests; and

6.3.3 To speed up your searches.

6.4 You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Website.

6.5 For information on how to control your cookies go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

6.6 Telephone calls to and from our any of our telephone numbers may be recorded for training and/or security purposes.

### 7\. Access To, and Amending, Your Personal Data

7.1 At any time, you can make a written request to us to have access to all the personal information that we hold about you. We reserve the right to charge you a small administrative charge should you make such a request; the current maximum charge is £10 for responding to a request.

7.2 You may inform us of any changes in your personal data and in accordance with our obligations to you by contacting us at privacy@rivalry.com. You can change relevant personal data through the “Account Settings” section within the Website. It is your responsibility to tell us when information that you have provided to us is out of date or needs to be amended, but we confirm that will update or delete your personal data accordingly.

### 8\. Closure of Your Account

If you close your Website account, we will retain the personal details that we hold about you for so long as is reasonably necessary in accordance with our legal and contractual requirements.

### 9\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

If we change any of the terms of this Privacy Policy in the future, we will post the amended Privacy Policy on the Website and, where appropriate, we will notify you by email. You should visit the Website periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or questions, regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@rivalry.com
